https://www.oakcreekprintworks.com/privacy-policy

Shopping Cart
0 item(s) - $0.00
Your shopping cart is empty!
Welcome visitor you can login or create an account.
Contact
All Mats, Foam Core Mount Boards, Glass/Plexiglas and Framing products are now exclusively available from our affliate, Special Delivery Frame Supplies. Each item now links directly to it's new home.
Categories
Accessories
- X-Acto Knives & Blades
Card Making
- Blank Cards
- Card Making Tools
- Envelopes
- Inkjet Cards and Paper
- Chocolate Brown
- Cream (Antique)
- French White
- Mist Light Grey
- Mocha (Tan)
- Photo Grey
- Sage Green
- Spanish White
- White - Black Core
- Specialty Mats
- Black - Red Core
- Brushed Gold Foil
- Denim Jeans Mats
- Frosted Mirror Mats
- Linen Canvas Mats
- Straw Hat Mats
Home
» Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
How Oak Creek Printworks uses and protects any information that you give Oak Creek Printworks when you use this website:
We respect the privacy of our users and will never share your personal information with a third party, unless you opt-in to receiving our online newsletter, in which case your name and email address only will be shared with our bulk email newsletter service.
We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. Please check this page from time to time to ensure that you are informed of any changes. This policy is effective beginning of May 1, 2014.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
Your name and company name
Contact information including email address
Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping
Improving our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, disabling cookies may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites we think may be of interest to our customers.  When you use one of these links, you will leave Oak Creek Printworks.  Oak Creek Printworks has no control over the content, protection or privacy of any other website.  Any information provided whilst visiting other websites does not fall under this privacy statement.  If you use one of these other sites, exercise caution and read the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
If asked to fill in a form on the website, click on the box to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time please contact us here.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties without your permission or are unless we are required to do so by law.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact us here.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible.  We will promptly make any corrections needed with the new information provided.
Information
FAQ
About
Shipping & Return
Privacy Policy
Terms & Conditions
Customer Service
Contact Us
Copyright © 2003-2020 Oak Creek Printworks. All rights reserved.
2961 E. Barnes St. • Simi Valley, CA 93065 • Voice: 805.522.5475
